Vue js it's a JavaScript framework for building front-end UIs in view you can
Vue js是一个用于构建前后端UI的 JavaScript 框架，
start simple and then progressively add in the tools and features that you need
从简单开始逐步添加构建复杂程序所需的工具和功能
to build a complex web application at its core it provides a way to build
它提供了一种通过JavaScript中的数据或状态来构建封装组件的方法
components that encapsulate data or state in your JavaScript and then
将该状态响应式地连接到HTML模板中
connect that state reactively to a template in HTML we call these
我们将这些组件称为声明式视图
components declarative views because the same data inputs will always produce the
当我们在它链接或绑定的数据对象上声明数据时
same output in the visual UI when we declare data on this data object it
相同的数据输入将始终在可视化UI中产生相同的输出
links or binds it to the HTML on the template above when the value of the
当数据的值发生变化时组件将自动重新渲染
data changes the component will automatically rerender or in other words
换句话说它是响应式的
it's reactive and the framework does a ton of work under the hood to make sure
并且框架在后台做了大量工作以确保这个过程
that this process is performance across a huge component tree we can work with
在数量众多的组件树中高效可靠的运行
this data in the template thanks to views HTML based template syntax we can
由于视图基于HTML模板，我们可以在模板中处理这些数据
interpolate a value for expression using double braces and we also have a variety
可以使用双括号为表达式插入一个值
of directives to control the behavior of the HTML based on the data we can use v-if
也有多种指令根据数据来控制HTML的行为
to only render an element when the value on the right side is truthy and then we
我们可以使用 v-if显示或隐藏元素
might have a fallback element after that that's only rendered when the values
我们可能会有一个后继元素只用于显示值，
fall C with v-else we can make the app interactive by listening to events using
这时我们可以使用 v-if,也可以通过使用 v-on 指令监听事件来使应用程序交互
the v-on directive we can listen to an event on an element then run some code
我们可以监听元素上的事件
to handle that event on the right side we can do that directly in the template
运行一些代码来处理右侧的事件，我们可以直接在模板中执行这些操作
or define a custom method and the components methods object the method has
或者定义一个自定义方法和组件方法对象，该方法可以访问我们的响应式数据
access to our reactive data and that means all we have to do is change the
这意味着我们所要做的就是更改数据的值
value of the data and the component will automatically rerender and that's all it
组件将自动重新渲染，这就是构建具有视图的交互式反应式声明性
takes to build an interactive reactive declarative UI component with view the
UI 组件所需的全部内容，该框架因其简单而受到开发人员的喜爱
framework is loved by developers for the simplicity but also its ability to scale
它还具有逐步扩展复杂性的能力，
up in complexity incrementally its plugin system allows you to easily drop
它的插件系统使您可以轻松地插入代码
in things like a router state management firebase support and more and perhaps
放入诸如路由器状态管理Firebase等等
best of all it's not sponsored by some mega corporation it's not pressured to
也许最重要的是它不是由一些大型公司赞助的，对于
push out new releases all the time and does a great job listening to its
持续推出新版本没有压力，并且
community this has been GU Jas and 100 seconds stay tuned for a full length
在倾听用户的声音这方面做的很好，这是Vue Js 的100秒简介
thanks for watching and I will see you in the next one
感谢观看，下次见